https://www.breadbeckers.com/blog/privacy/

Privacy – Bread Beckers
Open All Day Every DaySHOP ONLINE
305 Bell Park Dr Woodstock, GA 30188RETAIL STORE
Have Questions? We Can Help!1.770.516.5000
0 Item(s)
Rye
Sorghum (Milo)
Bug Repellant
Smokers (Outdoors)
Dehydration
Everything Apples!
Everything Chocolate!
Soup and Bread 2015
Soup!
Your Privacy
We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be used. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.
Questions regarding this policy should be directed to:
The Bread Beckers, Inc.
305 Bell Park Dr.
Woodstock, GA 30188
Tel: 770-516-5000
Email: (please use our HelpDesk link)
1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you?
We may ask you for personal information, including (but not limited to) when you: subscribe to our e-mail list, subscribe to our newsletter, send us a comment or an order. If you contact The Bread Beckers (by phone, e-mail, or in writing), we may keep a record of that correspondence.
2. What are cookies and how are they used?
Our on-line shopping cart system uses cookies to track your order up to the time you submit it.
Our Web Host does record the IP address of each visitor to our site, and keeps a record of the pages visited, etc. THE ONLY purpose of this is for us to analyze the usage of our website. Most individuals get a new IP address assigned to them (by their ISP) each time they access the internet; therefore, it is almost impossible for anyone to be “tracked”, unless they intentionally choose to leave their information.
We also use advertising services of AdRoll.com.  The AdRoll website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites.  AdRoll’s privacy policy is here.  To opt-out of their advertising, click here.
3. Who is collecting the information?
ANY information you leave with The Bread Beckers, Inc. is for our use alone. We do not share our customer information with anyone. If you choose to do business with us, or leave your name for our mailing list, it will stay with us.
If you are browsing our web site, see section 2 above.
4. How is the information used?
The Bread Beckers, Inc. only uses information to keep customers updated on seminars, demonstrations, new products, etc. Our accounting records are kept as required for tax and warranty purposes.  If you are browsing our web site, see section 2 above. AdRoll uses that information to help us market to you.
5. With whom may the information be shared?
For information we collect as part of doing business with you, we do not share that information.  If you are browsing our web site, see section 2 above. AdRoll uses that information to help us market to you.
6. What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of the information?
Any information you provide to the Bread Beckers, Inc. is kept on file in our offices. Email newsletter information, Helpdesk communications, class registrations, etc are each on hosted and maintained by separate providers – access to these systems are limited to certain staff members.
Search Recipes Articles Events
Search for:
Subscribe to BlogEnter your email address to be notified of new postsLeave This Blank:Leave This Blank Too:Do Not Change This:Your email:
Message from the Owners of Bread Beckers – Coronavirus COVID-19 Update
March 16, 2020
Archives Archives
Select Month
July 2020  (2)
May 2020  (1)
March 2020  (3)
June 2019  (1)
February 2019  (4)
December 2018  (1)
November 2018  (1)
September 2018  (11)
April 2018  (1)
March 2018  (4)
January 2018  (2)
November 2017  (1)
July 2017  (3)
June 2017  (3)
May 2017  (2)
April 2017  (1)
February 2017  (2)
January 2017  (1)
December 2016  (1)
November 2016  (1)
September 2016  (5)
August 2016  (2)
June 2016  (1)
May 2016  (8)
April 2016  (1)
March 2016  (1)
February 2016  (1)
January 2016  (3)
December 2015  (1)
November 2015  (1)
September 2015  (5)
July 2015  (6)
June 2015  (1)
April 2015  (2)
October 2014  (1)
May 2014  (1)
October 2013  (1)
June 2013  (2)
July 2010  (21)
August 2009  (2)
July 2009  (22)
1.770.516.5000Have Questions? We Can Help!
Retail Store305 Bell Park Dr Woodstock, GA 30188Open Mon - Sat 9am - 5pm
The Breadbeckers Inc.
All Rights Reserved. 	Privacy Policy Site by Greybeard Design Group
